We're going to discuss more about choosing
where to take the exam.
So if you go to a testing facility,
as you see on the next slide, you want to
make sure you know where the testing
facility is.
Doesn't hurt to do a dry run, you know,
a day or two ahead.
You want to make sure you get there at
least a half hour early.
You're going to have to check in,
show your ID.
It's often very cold in there.
So you'll probably want to wear a sweater.
But just know that if
you do before you go in,
you'll probably going
to have to take it off.
Turn it inside out.
They're going to check your pockets,
up the sleeves, your sleeves, your arms,
make sure you don't have any formulas,
your jeans pockets.
And if you wear glasses, maybe check to
make sure they're not Google glasses,
Google glasses, you know, because you can
get all kinds of information.
all right.
So they don't play.
So all your personal items must go in the
locker.
The only things you can take into the exam
itself, your locker key, and your ID.
That is it.
Everything else has to go into that
locker.
Your watch, your wallet, everything.
If you're diabetic or
something, you can put,
you know, food and
drink on top of the locker.
But they're going to watch you like a hawk
if you go back over there.
So try to eat ahead early if you can.
All right.
Also, don't drink too much coffee.
You're not going to be able to take very
many breaks.
All right.
So let's look at that third bullet again.
You can't take any personal items.
And yes, that includes pen, paper.
So most testing facilities have paper,
pencils, or a dry race board to use.
They also have a
calculator, usually in your
dashboard, or some of them
might have a hand held one.
but just know it will have add,
subtract, multiply, divide, that's it,
no scientific anything, but that will be
enough for what you need.
Online proctorate exam, which means again,
you'll be home at your table, your desk
with your computer or
laptop, but nothing can
be around you, nothing can be on the desk.
or walls.
They will look at everything.
All right.
No books, papers, anything.
I think the only thing you can have is a
glass of water on your desk.
All right.
And they will look around and make sure
they don't see or hear people either.
That's another big no-no.
All right.
So you have to have a webcam and it must
have your face visible at all times.
They're making.
making sure you don't
cheat, just like in the
testing facilities, there
are cameras everywhere.
So just know that you've got to have
Internet access and it has to be fast enough.
You'll have to check your links and stuff
first.
All right, but they give you all that
information.
All right.
As I mentioned before, no one else can be
in the room with you or near you,
seen walking by or hear any voices.
So make sure you don't have a TV on
nothing around.
you that could get you disqualified
remember no pins or paper we already
mentioned that you will have an online
whiteboard so yes no pins and papers in
the testing center not on your desk either
nothing you can only use the computer's
whiteboard like a dry erase
and you can use as your mouse
or if you have a laptop
your little keypad Thank you.